Hello, you guys are actually pretty brave to be in here
it's not
Not easy to be my friends sometimes, you know
because
Then you'll have other people
Talking about you and stuff, and I don't want to bring any
Any harm to you know my friends, but yeah, there's some interesting stuff happening. I
Keep trying to like
Well, I was trying to, you know, calm things down, you know, it's like, you know, I
Didn't start out by slandering anybody. I
Was very I was nice and actually I was like very apologetic and it's like I
until I started getting
Personally attacked I
Really didn't say much first let's address Christine
So Christine, I saw Christine this morning, she decided to come on, um, good times panel. I wasn't,
I didn't mention her at all when I talked to good times, but we talked about something else.
But Christine popped up and I was like, oh good, Christine, you know, and I,
I was, I was hoping, since I saw that she was, she laughed at the trip kick video,
that she had a sense of humor. Boy, was I wrong.
Um
You know she left the I mean that that triptych video. It was just the same exact thing
I think it was just me talking the thing all the same things except they added in some some witches and stuff like some
Witch effects and she was just laughing hysterically in their comments
And so I thought she had a sense of humor and plus, you know, let's not forget
She told me to jump off a bridge and she meant it right. She said she meant it
and so
I thought, oh, OK, well, she can joke around, right?
Even if she said she meant it, I think she's joking.
I really don't think she would want that, right?
But she said, no, I mean it.
I mean it.
But anyway, so she came on and started yelling at me
like an old grandma having a bad day.
And oh my gosh, you know what she told me?
She said, you're not allowed to talk about.
Um, Bida, or me, or Samman, or, um, Emma, or, uh, oh my god, it's a broken record.
And then she gets, oh, it's like, well, I can't talk about Steven Samman?
I mean, the guy who pornbombed me and, you know, Bida has shook my channel and.
I'm not allowed to talk about and be to who had a three-hour live and you were on that live talking about me, too
I'm not allowed to talk. Why are you allowed to talk about me and say the worst things about me?
I'm not allowed to though
And you know what I started out apologetic and I said, do you want to pull book apology? I'm sorry. I went too far
It was a joke and I know how to joke
Like, really? And she even, like, you know, I eventually just, like,
was like, you know what, leave me alone in this left.
But then she goes, you know what, he deletes all his lives.
And blah, blah, blah. I know. Only she can. Not me. Not me.
I delete all my lives. And you know what, Good Times is really good,
because he said, well, I know somebody else deletes all their lives, too.
You know who that is?
Oh, but she deletes every live. He only deletes some of it.
Now it's like look now. It's getting ridiculous. Okay, it's just getting ridiculous
and
I have a feeling that she was like this
Mystery source this other woman was talking to about how there's just this legion of women
I think it's like must be women be wait women from way before even my show that she's talked to you that are just like
Oh my god, he's doing it again. Oh, no. Oh
A heterosexual, it's like so strange.
We have all these, like, you know,
tons of men just sexually harassing women everywhere.
And it's like, I'm, I actually try to like turn it around
and kind of sexually harass men a little bit.
And it's like, they even have a problem with that.
Imagine.
I mean,
yeah.
Like it's like literal, I mean, it's like,
so I want to see what, I just want to know what Christine
My clips on oh, she said oh when he plays he thinks he can just play his old clips because they're his clips
Yeah
It's called my clips. I can play whatever I want. It's called my show
You have your show Christine where you know you do trivia with three people. It's fine. Like come on even cheese
Why do you have to be so pick on me and stuff? I mean it's like I don't understand like it's okay to like
fucking like put me through all this and it's like
Yeah, I know I made a ridiculous joke. I walked her through I walked her through the joke
She said he did not put the words in your mouth. I said clumsy said to me
Do you think beta and Christine are using you as like a ritual or something and I said
Oh, yeah
Because I you know I I stride into the ether and I saw you know her and and beta like you know make it around a tree
Sacrificing. I should have said baby goats. I said babies
But that was a bit
I mean
But maybe it's bad timing with this little stuff too. We'll get into that. Um
But I was like Christine
That's a joke, right? I said, did you tell me I should jump off of a bridge and stuff and I mean it I mean it
Okay, so that's not it. That's not even a joke, but I'm not allowed to joke
But you're allowed to tell me to do that, right?
second person by the way that says
But yesterday the second person yesterday said, you know what you should I'm actually never been conceived
Right, we and then we started talking my history until well. Yeah, we were having a great time
We had a great conversation and then all of a sudden ding dong
I'm thinking Maya, I appreciate that.
Ding dong, the witch is here.
You know what, I'm calling her a witch.
Do you know that this beautiful,
this like really devout Christian woman
was like, you know who's great?
Christine.
You know why?
Because she's a witch and I'm kind of a witch too.
But I'm, you know, I'm a Christian and stuff.
I don't, I don't know.
I thought in the Bible it said do not suffer a witch to live
but apparently it's really cool to be a witch
and have magical powers and stuff and blah, blah, blah.
I don't know.
Huh
You are
Well, you know what it's like
You can only do something to so many people and I know like a lot of people get cowed a little bit into like
You know silence and like you know, that's like oh my god
It's like I'll just I'll just shut up because it's like she's threatening all this stuff
You know what? I don't allow myself to be bullied and I'm going to stand up for not only me but like a lot of other people that are getting called just terrible things after being pretty much hoodwinked into this friendship.
I mean, it's like there's patterns. I see I recognize patterns. I see I look at patterns and stuff. And even before all this, I had been told about this.
And I was like, wouldn't it be interesting?
I was able to go through this process successfully
and maybe like, oh,
you have to change your name from the state.
Okay, well, I mean, it's like, I mean, I don't want,
I don't want to threaten her.
I don't want to, like I was threatened.
I was basically, last night I was told, you know,
I'm gonna have people beat me up. I'm gonna have I'm gonna probably be unalived. I
I should never have been conceived and all the every woman, you know, that she talked to agrees with that. I
There's something will happen that will be yeah, you know, did I ever like threaten anything? No
Never I think the most I said was I you know
I was like, I was sorry, and I said hi to her one night
in her chat.
She just went off on me.
Like, I was some monster.
And she calls me fraudulent psychic
instead of by even any name, fraudulent psychic.
Isn't that slanderous?
By the way, I'll just say from now on,
I'll just say my readings or whatever
are for entertainment purposes only.
Um, you know, I'm not claiming to like
Oh
Oh my gosh, well, see now it's getting crazy, but it's like see I mean there's really looky. It's like I
Don't I just don't know there. This is like it's getting crazy with like the accusation this lander, especially that one
It's like it's ridiculous. I mean in your mod and so you really like you have to look look at the rules in the chat
It's like I don't want like that accusation is brought up in whatever
it's like
I really would need you to contact me privately
about with paperwork or something like that,
not like make accusations in the chat.
Cause that just takes,
that's just distracting from everything right now, okay?
But anyway, cause you know,
I just see like a lot of that stuff,
you know, beat is being called that name too.
Okay. Oh, I just don't know.
I mean, it's like,
Just see people in the chat. I'm not endorsing it or whatever anything anybody's saying in the chat, right? I just want
You know not to I
Mean it's like, you know, it's crazy. It's getting crazy guys getting crazy. I don't and then the
Let's let's like save that stuff really. Let's like let's like try to just keep things safe for everybody right now. Okay, but
You know, I was called I was called, you know, I
smell
I'm just filthy inside and out. My soul is filthy. I
I
endorse the sacrifice of
children
The murder of children or something like that. I
Am so ugly so it warns, you know people to stay away from me
I'm just like
The scum of the earth like I don't know
How did how did it come to that from like?
Her being my biggest supporter. So I have a couple ideas about that
So let's have a like a little presentation. It's called it's not a video. It's just a slideshow. It's quick slideshow
Good afternoon careless Kate. How are you? I'm gonna click quick slideshow. This is called
You see if I can find it. Okay. This is a slideshow called
Bring it up they're working. Hi Kate. Good to see ya. Thank you for being here
This is a little slideshow. It's not very long. It's just a quick little slideshow that should be very informative
Okay, so just bring that down
Just uploading just give it a second. Okay. So anyway, and then I'll read the public statement or whatever and then
I mean, but the Christine stuff, it's like after all,
after I was dealing with that all night
and just like, you know, in this traumatic,
like just like, I had just heard these shocking,
shocking like accusations level against me.
Like I was like, had been,
I got some like a rapist or something, right?
I just, oh, Chuck Norris died.
Okay, but God bless Chuck Norris.
Let's welcome, let's watch the buddy troll presentation.
Shit, hold on, let's go back.
So the what is a buddy troll where it says this is when the troll wears the face of a friend
Then the trust becomes the weapon and intimacy becomes the trap. Okay
So what is the buddy troll so it's called relational trolling trust is a weapon not the shield
And so here's some of the stages it goes through.
So it starts at the entry point where they do not attack
from the outside, they enter as an ally, a fan,
confidant, helper, supporter, or a real one.
And they emphasize relational access and rapport
to blend in, okay?
So that builds trust pretty fast.
But they have an arsenal.
So they operate through trust, access,
emotional ambiguity, and relational leverage,
not chaos or random aggression.
they use subtle influence rather than overt force and so it's not the normal troll who like
pretty much reveals themselves instantly as a troll they have you know they have other other
tools they use so the strategy is not random chaos trolling it's strategic calculated relational
manipulation with patience measured moves that exploit bonds and momentum because they want to
Because most people will not be prepared for this, right?
But there is a danger.
The threat comes from the inside of the relationship itself.
The danger is proximity, not distance.
Intimacy becomes the vector for harm.
OK, let's continue.
So they have a disguise.
And it's usually called a mask, right?
A mask.
And so this is how they present.
The performance is friendliness, not hostility, right?
Because especially.
people that have like me that have just like you know been kind of traumatized by relationships in the past and like
Have a lot of hostility towards them having someone friendly come in
is like, oh, it's like, oh, my gosh, somebody that understands somebody that, you know,
finally, like, you know, the one person that see that seat and
Yeah, and I can give so many examples of this but I'll just go to my personal stuff after this maybe a little bit
But but they weren't first on it. They were warm funny and unusually available
They validate. They're very honest and other pretty anti-drama and they're you get a bond fast faster than feels really natural
It's just like a quick. It's just like it goes very fast, right?
And they adopt some roles like the biggest public supporter
the translator to the group and
The secret source of protection from the haters, okay?
your secret source of protection from the haters, right?
So our secret source as in, you know,
maybe like really behind the scenes
helping you out with some stuff, right?
And, but they have some entry techniques.
Let's go up, let's go up, is it a, yeah, is it a,
you know, I guess it works both ways
with either up or down this ladder,
but let's go start from the top.
It says, you know, they start with love bombing,
overwhelming attention,
and which creates an immediate emotional bond.
You know, love bombing is a very effective tactic,
especially as a narcissistic abuse.
It's like when it's basically the idealization phase where it is like
It's basically like you know how like a little little bit of some love feels good imagine like a lot of love
It's like oh my gosh. This is like it's like gonna
Feels great, right?
Everyone loves to be loved right and be treated well, but and then there's mirroring so they actually
Reflect your language your opinions your wounds and your humor to manufacture connections like they'll say
You know, I was told that I'm I was told these same things about me
I know things like this and I can go more into it
but their strategic vulnerability they share some secrets with you to gain your trust and
reciprocity and
You feel obligated to reciprocate when they
When they share their secrets because when someone shares their secrets or you're talking about some of your secrets, too
Because we just had the psychological
Need for reciprocity normal people, right? They're also insider flattery. I get you like nobody else does I get you like the others
You have an exclusive understanding of a special relationship
These private channels that I mean they'll use like a different probably a different channel than the main channel you use
Maybe they might say oh go to here's my here's my I'm specials specials social media site or they'll write you on you know
X if you're you know if you use YouTube or they'll use
Instagram or something like that, but Instagram is an interesting feature. It's called disappearing messages
And when I saw that the person was using disappearing messages,
I was like, that's interesting.
Like, why do they want their messages to disappear?
Is that going to be something in the future I should maybe worry about?
Private channels.
Yeah. And so, yeah, exactly.
Okay. So then there's the premature loyalty.
They offer their loyalty before the, you know, they earned it and that bypasses the time
it takes to actually build trust in the normal way.
Okay.
So let's continue.
We have the core methods.
Boundary testing, the insular tester limits and in tiny doses with plausible deniability.
So it's not too obvious, right?
They might have some aggression or some like just little jokes, but they're just joking, you know
It's just like you know cute little little delivers attacks wrapped in humor with built-in escape routes. So it's like
There's no way they can like really be
It's a very easy for you to say. Oh, that was just a joke for sure because I'm I know they I know I can trust them
right there's concern trolling they disguise manipulation as a as care and protective worry and
selective agreement so
They will mix their support with little subtle
Undermining which kind of creates a little bit of confusion, but not too much of it. I mean, it's very very subtle
I'll say because too much will kind of throw things off.
It's like they need you to be hooked in
because this is called, I mean,
they're playing a long game, right?
So they'll fish for disclosure.
They'll extract emotional vulnerabilities.
They'll find out what all your insecurities are,
what bothers you most about what people are saying.
What are your own insecurities?
What are your traumas?
Like they'll,
They just close this and they'll learn this through a process over the relationship, you know, through these midnight talks or, or, you know, special time together and things like that they use triangulation, which is using third parties.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, and I'm only saying is because you care this person this person this person, right?
And so you have to watch out with that for everybody because there'll be other people with their own motives for the triangulation
Okay, and let's see visual metaphor. So they have these
Yeah, so the visual metaphor think of hooks think of strings think of keys think about marionette wires
Those are tools of control designed as tools of connection because what they're connected
the marionette in their mind, right?
You're just, because they can actually know
your emotional triggers and all this stuff
and be able to kind of push you around.
The style of the Buddy Troll is ambiguity
over the spectacle, erosion over explosion.
They operate through being a little bit ambiguous,
like it's basically like, not too,
nothing's too obvious, it's like, and so,
and things are like, oh, I can interpret it as this,
I can interpret it as that,
and you choose to interpret it in a positive way,
You know, it's so it's not a direct attack
They use the ambiguity the soft language with sharp outcomes and an emotional fog
I would say it's like a fog machine kind of like that
No fog when his fog needs to it stands for fear obligation and guilt and other big narcissistic abuse
Abuse tool they'll prioritize some kind of intimacy first
So the private influence before the public damage because they have this public damage planned already, right?
But that's the stage
two or three, right? But they have to first, you know, you have the influence on you. You're not
going to have any influence if you don't trust them. So they'll have to do anything they think
will gain that trust. So there's intimacy over the spectacle. And there is a control, not a chaos.
Okay. So the goal is this erosion, this like wearing away. They want you to doubt yourself
while still defending them. You don't need to be off balance, but not destroyed.
and it's like there's an emphasis on the erosion over the sudden collapse so it's a slow burn
it's like it's slow it's like because it's like you know and things go slow it's like
You don't really notice it because it's like it's like going so slow and then it's like but before you know it
You're like, you know, like someone's polishing something with sandpaper, right?
You just go slow and it's a little bit of time a little bit of time and then it's like but all of a sudden, you know
Oh, they took too much from there, right?
Just putting that's on your heart. So they do not always want a visible explosion
They want sustained power through your uncertainty, right because the explosion will kind of like
you know end things too quickly this is this is a long game after all oh here we go the long
game so there's eight stages to this long game it's from the access to the exploitation it's
patient it's not impulsive and so we have you know they spot the target they look for someone
open visible lonely trusting and under pressure so they'll see this person oh look that person's
kind of like you know being bullied isolated you know needs him needs somebody like you know
I can like come in as this hero, right?
So they'll gain the access to become useful,
trusted, emotionally familiar.
They'll do whatever it takes for you to trust them, right?
And then all of a sudden they'll vanish.
They'll flip the narrative or return later as a friend.
And they'll map out your vulnerabilities.
They'll learn your wounds, right?
And the ambitions.
This is a long process, by the way, guys.
This is called, this part is like really the long game.
There is buddy trolling that is like more
quick like you know you'll pretty much figure out quickly that they're they're like you know putting
you down and stuff but the long game is like they will pretty much put on wear this mask and the
mask won't really won't crack very much they'll be very careful about that um so they will learn
your wounds ambitions insecurities and conflicts because
With these, these are your weaknesses.
These are all our weaknesses.
These are our weak points, the things that bother us,
the good things that would hurt us the most,
the things that are most important to us, right?
They'll learn where they can hurt you.
They'll learn your like little weak spots
where to dive in the knife, right?
So then they'll exploit and expose you.
They'll use that gathered intel for their status,
their entertainment to sabotage you or control you.
Then they'll shape your reality.
They'll influence your moods, beliefs, reactions,
and relationships, and destabilizing.
They introduce doubt, shame, confusion, and conflict,
and they'll create a dependency too.
They'll become your interpreter, your validator,
your gas, or your gatekeeper.
I was gonna say gas later, but there, gatekeeper.
You know, it's like, and whatever it takes
really to gain this trust.
Okay, and so this timeline is measured in months
and sometimes years, not in moments.
But each willing is patient, okay?
They're waiting for certain certain little
Landmarks in the relationship where they'll go to the face and so this is like what they really want their gold may not be destruction
Often just keeping you off balance and below them
Isn't that interesting?
Don't maybe they don't want to really want to
And I'm destroying you, but they do want you below them. It's like they do want to be higher
They do want to be like considered like better and you just be considered bad. How do they do that?
They give you attention that you know, they make you the center of your emotional focus without appearing needy. There's a ductive
It's predatory as predatory layering. Okay, and then they'll exercise this control. Okay?
And this relational, so they will control the perception, the moods, relational dynamics as a controller stabilizing force.
They use it as entertainment, so they feed on reactions and emotional drama as a spectator sport, amplifying chaos for sport.
They want social dominance, right?
So they establish this hierarchy
while appearing friendly and supportive.
They always have to be above you.
They're the one that's coming in as a savior.
They're helping you.
They're the one that is like so good and rich
and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And maybe they'll pull you up a little bit,
but it's like still,
it's always gonna be below them, right?
They'll get access to your secrets.
So they're gathering this intel for leveraged status
or future use, a quiet accumulation of power,
getting this access to secrets,
this disclosure from you, and I created dependency on you,
with you, right?
So they make you need their validation and, you know,
or their interpretation, their emotional stability,
just their friendship.
Okay, here's a critical insight sometimes the goal is not destruction and sustained influence
They can win by keeping you on balance and subordinate not visibly damaged
But if they start to feel that they're losing that influence, that's when they'll start another stage, right?
That's and these other stages are just are bad. Okay, but here's some red flags and pattern recognition
Just to help me read this slice. This is almost over. So they'll rush closeness. So it will be a little love bombing
They'll rush the relationship and you'll notice very fast
parts of the relationship and you'll be like, whoa, this is faster than normal.
If this is happening so fast, this must be fate. This must be ordained. So they'll rush to
closeness. They'll know too much too fast. They'll push intimacy at an accelerated timeline.
They're assuming subtle isolation. They'll separate you from other relationships while
uh, the innocence, right?
If, uh, they provoke you and then they're innocent, right?
So they'll provoke a reaction and then they're like,
I didn't mean to do episode star. Oh my gosh.
Oh, I didn't know about that, right?
They'll get shocked and hurt by your response.
Wow. Did that ever happen after a provocation?
Like maybe like, you know,
when you're friends and you've not had a problem,
they put on an AI of you, you know,
dirty on the couch with the cats,
with your cats, they don't steal money from banks
and say, oh, this is what the person dreams about.
When it's like, you're like, what?
Like, what's that about you?
And then, then it's like, what?
I'm shocked, it might hurt by my response, right?
Invisible scorekeeping, they keep score of the layers
and loyalty, or their favors and loyalty,
but they'll frame it as honesty, right?
So...
They will be keeping track of everything they give you everything they do for like and then it's like then they'll be ready to say look
What I did off an itemized list, right? This is all so kidding home
Okay, then they'll be a public and then a private or or they'll be both at the same time a public and private split
There'll be a private insensitivity and then a public innocence
Conflict follows them, but it's never their fault
And then there's recognition key.
So you feel ungrateful and uneasy at the same time.
So you trust the pattern,
or you feel grateful and uneasy at the same time, right?
Cause it's like, wow, I just been given these great gifts,
but then it's like, oh, like, is there a price to this?
There's a hidden cost that I'll have to be paying soon.
Plus I haven't, I've been warned
about this exact thing happening.
Okay.
Finally, there's a defense guys.
And so you take this to heart
It's happened to me.
So the antidote is pattern recognition, okay?
Pattern recognition, recognizing these patterns.
I hope you just take note of some of these today.
Boundaries, refusing to confuse familiarity with trust.
So take it slow and document.
Slow the pace of the intimacy deliberately with them.
Do not over disclose early in a relationship.
Document patterns instead of isolated moments.
Hey, why did they do this every time?
Why did they do this every time?
Is this happening?
Has this happened in other people
in the same pattern, right?
You watch consistency across time and settings.
You set some boundaries that have independence, so you can hear their private behavior with
their public behavior, refuse loyalty tests and ultimatums to maintain your independent
relationships outside of their influence, and set a boundary once clearly and then enforce
your boundary.
Finally, do that pattern recognition where you trust the patterns that you're seeing over
the individual incidents that are happening.
You notice what you're feeling.
If you're feeling grateful and uneasy at the same time,
that's like this cognitive dissonance
that's telling you something.
You reduce access without dramatizing it.
You just like slowly maybe like back away a little bit
and remember familiarity and just, you know,
knowing them, being very familiar with them
and thinking you know them so well.
It's not the same as trust
and that doesn't mean you've earned the trust.
So the buddy troll wins through access, ambiguity and time.
Your antidote is recognizing the patterns,
having clear boundaries and refusing to confuse.
Familiarity with trust and that is the presentation. Okay, and I hope you guys enjoyed that you're medically retired
Let's see what's going on in the chat Schumann link
Link the stuff does sound very familiar. Yeah, doesn't it?
I mean, it's like it is like the same very similar to the narcissistic abuse cycle. Yes mental and emotional manipulation
Yeah
Oh my gosh, Shannon, hi, Yasmina.
I think that's a fake Kate, or not the fake Kate,
the fake Yasmina, sorry, that's fake Yasmina.
The fake Shannon, hey Jesus Christ.
It's like, I didn't say, oh, and so are cats.
My cats are, you know, hey, preside, how are you?
And I hope you did enjoy that little quick presentation
as for like a little statement.
I'll make a statement. I don't know how much I want to talk about it after the statement, but let's have a little statement
This will be my public statement on the on the thing you can go and watch the statements that were made last night
So I want to address something directly and clearly a number of false hostile and the famatory things have been said about me publicly
I reject those statements completely. I'm not going to answer smear tactics with more smear tactics
I'm not going to let other people to find my character my intentions or my work for me
So let me be clear, I'm not afraid, I'm not intimidated, and I will continue to speak the truth,
but I will do so in a more disciplined way, no hysteria, no mob mentality, no games,
but if the happening is a pattern, there's been some projection, distortion, personal attacks,
insinuation made, and attempts to turn accusations into entertainment.
So I'm not participating in that circus, people can judge me by my actual words, my actual conduct,
my body of work I put out publicly, not by somebody else's performance.
I also want to make something clear, this show is not a place for threats, harassment, doxing,
or revenge behavior. So do not contact, threaten, or target anyone on my behalf, please.
That is not what I want, and that is not what the platform is for.
But I will protect my name. I will document what needs to be documented. I will continue
forward with clarity. I'm here to create to speak honestly and tell my own story in my own voice
and that is all I need to say on it right now. And I think that's uh, that's good. Okay, so
you went to link. Okay, so Arthur, how about the link? Okay, but Arthur
Okay, he said please. I mean, he did say please. Hey, hey Brad. What's my thoughts on files? Oh the FCM files FCM files
I'm skeptical, but I'm I mean I'm seeing now. It's like there's bodies being found. There's these like, you know
these like
Regen these rings where there people are like, you know making babies and stuff. We have Long Island ice-teed
Hey, Benny. How are you? Good to see you. What's up, dude? I'd say
What's up, brother? Can I say something and I hope it doesn't piss you off?
Say it.
I think that was the best use of AI you've ever done. Like everything you've said,
that the manipulating, the false.
Well, that wasn't all AI. I mean, it's like, I did it.
Let's see. I'll put it this way. I don't use AI. I work with AI. I don't just
Well, that was the best use of AI.
Wait, why didn't you say that?
Like, why can't you just say that the content and not
the method I produced it, it's like, you know, you say,
oh, that's a nice guitar.
But, you know, right?
Go ahead.
But, you know, does a guitar really matter
as long as the sound is good?
Like, tell me.
That was great, though.
The narcissism was perfect, right?
Who, mine?
The narcissism and the last, no, no.
I'm saying the way you.
You detailed it. You explained to us how to identify narcissism
Yeah, okay. Well, but like you see I was very helpful
I was able that was an outline, but I was able to put my own words to it too and explain it like in oh, nice
Okay, that's a perfect example of a buddy troll that's Arthur, okay
So Arthur is a buddy troll so he will come and he'll buddy up to you see this little subtle things
Like the little subtle things he said he'll even say beforehand. Oh, don't get offended, right?
And it's like, so you know something's coming, right?
This is a great example and he'll pretend to be your friend, right?
But then he will just fucking try to like embarrass you like make you look stupid fuck you over
I mean, it's like really but he'll be so nice about it, too. I mean, it's like he does suck
Yeah, it's like, you know, like and why do I have you up, right?
Yeah, bad timing for the buddy trolling Arthur, when I'm doing, yeah, when I'm doing the fucking presentation on buddy trolling, and you come up with buddy troll.
Do you think I don't, do you think I didn't just pay attention to my own presentation?
I just learned so much from my entirely AI generated presentation. I haven't been through it and have experience or anything.
Um, I just, I just, um, I just learned about it today, right? Okay.
What an asshole. What an asshole, completely.
Anybody else want to come up? Can I have a real friend up for something like that? I don't know
I'm like kind of I'm kind of getting weary of
Whatever this is whatever that is, you know Arthur I have a great person for you me go go hand with Alexandra
I think I think he would love her. Okay. Oh
He does yeah, I don't know. I will Arthur. I think donated $5, you know last January. So, you know
Okay, thank you, Kate, I know.
Yeah, I know.
I mean, it's just like, I feel like,
but I'm not in a minstrel show, Arthur.
I mean, should I get my cane in a hat
and go use some more tap dancing around?
You think I'm like, have you heard the things
that have been said, Arthur?
Arthur, first of all, go watch what was said first, okay?
Then come back and try to buddy troll me, okay?
You're the definition of a buddy troll we know I see you run over to beat us and it's like I know I know
I think you sound like sometimes like you're defending me and stuff like that. You're just trying to stir up shit
A menstrual show, yeah, that's when Minnie Manson takes off his pad and takes a picture of it for the camera.
I'm just kidding. A menstrual show is actually, wait, wait, the menstrual flow, yeah, exactly.
A menstrual show is like when they do blackface and they do like, you know,
they have this thing called the menstrual interloculator and they do like tap dancing and blah, blah, blah.
Yeah. So, I don't know if you've ever seen, you've seen, it's a kind of like old-fashioned and they're considered very racist.
They used to I think it took I think it originated somewhere in Freemasonry. I
Don't think I know
Okay, anyway, so anybody anybody else anybody else? What's this about? Oh
My god 14 comments in the back chat
Let's see you love me if you love me why do you do that to me? It's like I just I just don't like if you love me
Why can't you just like?
You know that's gonna irritate me like subtly, right?
But now it's like it's the past. It's about it. It's a vagina monologues. Yeah
Hold on
Hold on what
What
I'm sorry I phrased it wrong. I was trying to say because look I definitely used chai gbt a lot
Okay, get out of here out of here
Don't come back you're kicked out. Bye
Hello
Thank you, what's up brother? How you been? I'm just fine. I'm just fine. Oh my god
Can everybody okay, I sound like shit, bro
If I'm fine. Oh, who's the victim? Of course the fake boob old bag is talking about it. Okay, but how about like, you know
But also Christine and stuff is like, you know, Christine said
How dare you talk to Sandman?
Like I'm talk about Sam. You're talking about Sam and did he who else Emma. Why don't I guys I hear the same like
It's like I recognize these things like I said, I'm not bought like I'm really not bothered by what it said because I've had I've had
The worst bullying already. I've been through bullying all my life, right? I'm a gay person, right?
Who's how to the closet? I've always been through. I've always been bullied. It's the fact that
There's the attempt is being made. That's what really hurts. Okay, and then here comes black arches like buddy troll you
Jay dog might be I'm them. No, no, no, I'm not nobody troll bro. I've always been cool with you, bro
I've always been I I'm sorry. I probably sound like shit, bro
I've been sick for like the last week and a half two weeks. I've had fucking bad pneumonia and fucking
Did you see your
You're the video that you're in with me
Chipping video. I think I did the cult. Yes. Yeah, like a couple of them. There's there's a Rajneesh. Okay. Okay. Oh, great
Here's um, here's sake. Let me just let me just ban him from the studio. Okay, perfect. Oh
Oh, you're yeah, you're yeah, perfect. Okay, and
I thought we were friends too, but it's called man. It's a buddy troll
Like you see he comes on and like says that shit to me
What are they? What do they do bro? What are they they're fucking with you bro? What are they doing?
Should I read some of the transcript of what was said last night? I mean, it's like I think you should bro
Cuz I'm out of the loop on any of this shit. I don't know what's going on
I just know that you know a lot of shit in the fan
Hold on a second. Yeah, there is some stuff said last night. Let me just get the transcripts because I don't want to play
Okay, and I'll read some of it, let me see I just need to
Go take a minute, so go ahead and talk, but I hope you're feeling well.
Yeah, I mean, you see the cartoon about yourself on Lord of the Groove, where you're like,
you're growing over some interesting stuff.
Well, I think I've seen the video before yeah, you used to be subscribed to them because my video my whole channels got hit
My heck both of them got taken out. I do sound so you're sick today. Yeah. Yeah, I'm still sick man
I just wanted to come on here and just let you know that you know, I'm your friend, bro
I'm I've never been a buddy troll not to you, you know
I wasn't referring to you
I mean, I think you've been pretty cool. It's yeah, so many of we both knew you know, but um, hold on one sec
I just need to get a I need to put a password in for this whole day. I have this uh, well, yeah
No, so yeah, I'm still around guess my channel's got here and I'm just
Channels down or you're just not able to stream
No, both my channels got here this I think beta hit them or somebody hit my channel
They got coffee like truck. Well the copyright check will tell you who did it
It was some Arab guy, so I don't know if it was beat as X or you know, I really it wasn't even worth it to me
I just said, you know, fuck it. I could still go on panels. I don't know, you know, okay
I know his I know his name it starts with an M. Oh, I think it starts
I think it starts with an M. Is that start with an M?
It was a really long name. I could be honest. I would to be honest. I was just like frustrated. I just said, you know what?
Fuck it. I'm not like
Okay, it was more trouble than it's worth. That's all I'm just gonna say fuck it. It wasn't worth it to me
That's why I just but yeah, I'm here for you psyche. I'm here, bro. I'm here
And yeah, I am I am bro. I'll start another channel. See ya people. I'm still out here. So yeah
You too, bro
I mean, um, yeah, I just, I do like, you know, like J-Dog and he was with me, but, um, okay, hold on.
Okay, so I do have this, some of the chance, here's what was said last night, a little bit of what was said.
I'll address some of it, you know, it's like, but I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna harp on it.
I'm not gonna attack the person. I'm just gonna use the words they said, okay?
Okay, so it says, here's what I want to say.
There's this rumor.
I'm going to call it a rumor within these communities
that I have a certain cycle.
Okay.
And then blah, blah, blah.
She was defending against that.
Okay, hold on.
And so I'm not gonna,
I'm just gonna like read the parts about me.
So it says,
So a guy that used to be known by the name of Q45 now his name is Q
I heard him say tonight, but I'm hearing this fraudulent psychic say it um who um myself and several other women
Wish was never conceived and here's what I want to say and okay, and then she says it lets you be my person
You don't know me. Okay. I did meet the person in person. So that doesn't apply to me. Okay, and it says
And as much as they trash talk to me,
there's enough confidence, hold on.
It says, let's see, but you know what?
If you have not met me in person,
you don't know what you're talking about.
And if you have met me in person,
but you're definitely a fraud, a solid criminal,
and a con artist, such as the fraudulent psychic,
you don't have any business talking to me.
But...
Guess some people are holding on to this false hope they're not that I'll communicate with them again one day
Or I'll be friendly with them or if enough time goes by. I'll forget about things. No
No, anyone I would forgive has already been forgiven
There are people who seem to be under the impression that I talk to certain people more than I do
People like to say good times for life as someone that I've cycled. No, no, no good times and I don't talk at this point
All I do is point out when he says something valid.
And what's wrong with that?
I've never met him in person.
We're all not friends,
but we've been around for a long time.
But the fraudulent psychic,
well, you just give it a rest.
Okay, because I've spoken to enough people at this point
who have dealt with you.
To where you might end up following through
with that threat you made the other day
in regards to yourself.
Because you've done too much to too many women who did not know how to contend with the kind of monster that you are
Here's what's going on with these communities right now
You know how it seems like there's a certain group that all came to the same place in the same time and caused a lot of trouble
Really amped with the stalking started monetizing the panels in a very unethical way
Meaning the clap system the vesting crap
vetting behind the scenes, getting people to pay to join panels or join
discords, all that kind of stuff, even though they pretend to be at odds with
each other in some cases, these people will all do work together. There's a lot
of people with deep pockets right now looking at these communities and some
of these people with deep pockets have approached some of these really aggressive
people and people came in of and
They're like, okay, let's try to formulate an offshoot.
That's lucrative.
But there needs to be like basically
a cast of characters, right?
So trust me when I say,
there have been people with deep pockets
looking at these communities.
They're looking at who's been around the chart
or the longest,
who's controllable, who's not controllable,
who's skilled and talented, who's not,
who's professional, who absolutely needs not to be dealt with.
That's what's been going on,
I'd say for maybe a year and a half now,
maybe even longer.
But from what I've learned, the fraudulent psychic
was paid a certain amount of money to basically create a sort of cast.
And there are some people he was asked to approach
who saw right away, no, no, no, this is not feeling good.
This is negative.
This is not what I want.
And those seem to be the people
that he has most aggressively condemned,
defamed, lied about, right?
When someone tells you no, you respect that
and you're leaving the fuck alone to that fraudulent psychic.
You're never going to be able to deliver
when it comes to me.
And someone who approached you is aware of that now.
So you're not going to get any more money from that person.
That person does not want to be named.
So you really need to fuck off because sometimes when someone who is mentally unstable as you are
doesn't know how to stop.
The people who talked to you not long ago, they'll stop you if you catch my drift.
So if you don't stop, something's gonna happen to where it will never be able to be undone because
I don't like what you're doing.
I don't like who you are.
There are so many other things that could have said about you that I have not said.
But what I will say is that a person who is filthy externally is filthy in spirit.
So there will be no cycle. I will never be your friend.
And just like the other women, especially Elisa, Elisa Jordana, told you to fuck off.
Get lost. Keep my name out of your mouth. I'm saying it too.
There have been a lot of women who know about you, even before you entered these communities.
And you scared some of them, you know. That's why you're ugly.
It is. That's why. It's basically a warning sign from God and more people need to pay attention to your external
So they know how disgusting you are internally. Seriously. There's enough young people in these communities
to where I'm sure you'll be able to fool them, but not me. Just like you weren't able to fool the other women who um,
US scared to death, honestly.
And a lot of those women are about to come forward
because they're seeing what I'm contending with
when it comes to you.
And they're not happy about it.
They're like, he's doing this again,
and it's like, yep, again, so just fuck off.
Trust me, when I say there's enough people
in these communities who are godless,
who are desperate, who are unprofessional,
who are just disgusting as you are,
but none of you are going to get anywhere professionally.
You're never gonna make any money, you're dying.
So Q was got it right.
The only way to make money in these communities,
you have to have a bunch of Alexes, fraudulent psychic.
You're not gonna get any more Alexes or anyone good.
The only person who definitely is completely banned
from my platforms is probably that girl, Kate.
And I didn't realize that she was in line with you
as she is, which is very concerning
and downright disgusting.
I liked her for a little bit, but not now.
The whole thing is revolving around Lilith
was a little tip-off.
Do some of you know who that deity Lilith is?
And I know y'all are in chat, so I'm just,
I'll address you later.
I just wanted to get what's in my head out.
The Lilith, the monster demon.
It's not a deity, it's a demon.
It's not a saint.
It's nothing like that.
It's not the first woman.
It's a demon.
That's a demon known to kill children.
Why in the hell would you worship a demon
known to kill children?
And that's the worst kind of evil that exists.
Any of you think about that?
I mean, I guess you're not into God.
If you're not into Jesus Christ.
If you're not Christian, you don't give a shit.
Okay, fine.
I don't want nothing to do with you.
There's people in other walks of faith
who are not Christian, who know what it is,
and they don't want anything to do with someone
who's into that.
So, I mean, that's what this community
have had the blessing of covering
or succumbing to now, a literal cult,
whose deity is a demon known to kill children.
Mm-hmm, that's gross.
That is gross.
That is absolutely gross.
When it comes to the person that you just named, the junkie, I don't have anything else to say
about that. I think I made that stream about that earlier today. I don't care. He aligned with a
fraudulent psychic. As soon as someone aligns themselves with that kind of energy, no, no, no.
It's okay if you didn't know. I'm just telling you. I'm telling you. But even if you don't
subscribe to any form of spirituality or faith, I'm sure that all of you are listening to me,
whatever reason, do understand the reality of money, okay? These people who recently came in
cause all kinds of problems.
They're looking for money
and they can't get it on their own
because they're not skilled.
They're not talented.
Nobody likes them.
They're not attractive people.
They don't have any sort of anything.
They don't know how to socialize properly.
They don't know how to do anything.
They need you.
You don't need them.
So all I'm saying is that
realize your worth because I know my worth.
I didn't always, but now I do.
And like hell, I'm gonna let some piece of trash
try to corral me.
It's weird.
It's actually attempted slavery.
And I'm a descendant of people who said notice slavery,
adamantly, and it was the Jews behind slavery
in the United States, whether you acknowledge it or not.
Bunch of nasty ass Jews.
So, I'm fraudulent psychic.
Fuck off, you don't know me.
I hope that some people in these communities do meet you in person, so they can see exactly
what I saw in regards to what you are, because you have a lot of very spiritually strong people
in these communities, a lot of Christians. They don't always admit that they are, but they are.
And considering some of the crap you've pulled, you're probably going to get physical with you
should you decide to meet any of them in person, especially the males.
And not the physical in the way you'd probably like.
But, you need to stop. Do your, um, what you call a show. Without me, you're going to get a knock on the door soon in regards to some legal actions.
And all you have to do is stop. Leave me alone. I've been so nice. I really have.
My channel, like I said, is 40 plus.
Okay, well I just want to see how the reaction is so far. So how are we doing in the chat?
Where's my oh yeah, is this it?
Okay, hold on. Oh, here we go. Hi guys
How are we doing? Oh
RG's here
Hey, I was hoping to talk to J-Dog because he's he's blatantly lying about his channels getting taken down
He deleted both of them
Why he would make that up? I don't know. I have screenshots to prove it J-Dog. It's just strange anybody know who DK TV is
DK I do not
Um, secondly, uh, psyche, oh, I'm sorry.
You know, I'm not a body troll because most of the time I try to give you good advice
and you get mad at me.
That's the opposite of being a buddy troll.
Here, here's how you give advice.
Arthur is like, you use so much AI and something.
Hey, use AI too, Arthur.
My criticism on AI has nothing to do with being a buddy troll.
Arthur's a blink and blink.
What do you say like in last night and good times?
You said, you said, you said, yeah, that sure is sick.
What were you referring to as sick?
Like, were you referring to a sick last night?
I was talking to a good, I don't like good times.
It has nothing to do with you.
Okay.
But you're so lost that that was I was reading a transcript sparkly by long water. Yeah. Oh, that's another thing
I listened to that streamed live. Uh, first of all had zero views. No one was there watching Alex
So you just double the for people who talk 50 views now. So okay
That's nothing. How many views is your video gonna have triple that by the time you're done with it, right?
That doesn't matter because I it doesn't matter. I wonder is now that many people more people heard it talking about me and people, okay
Well, because she wants you to be upset. She wants to get this reaction on you.
I'm upset. I'm very passionate about this, right?
You're feeding into it, is my point.
Okay, shut up. Get out of here. I don't want to talk to you right now.
Okay, and let me see who this is right here. Hold on a second.
Don't tell me what to do. If I want to feed into it, let me feed into it.
Hello?
Barry?
Barry, are you going to talk? Hello, you're on the air with Psyche.
Hello
Barry okay, Bant
At least like know how to talk. I mean geez RG
Arthur's a buddy troll
Yeah
I'm never gonna get McDonald's from him. I'm having my menses. Oh, oh
Who's rude?
Bathory your rude Bathory
Is RG a buddy troll?
Definitely, because he also uses other people
to do his beduri work.
He's like, oh, he's like, uh, remod,
or let Mike Hall in your chat.
Mike Hall has said horrible things to me.
Like, that leading me to think
that he's an ally of Master Computer.
Why would I let him in my chat?
I want people to hear.
I want, do you know that she told Good Times and I
that we'd be thrown into an oven?
Because we're Jews. Did you hear that? Hello here? I'm just gonna play this video real quick. I made this video
Okay, I mean if it clears out some people that's absolutely fine because probably not my friends anyway
And our bathroom you're breaking the rules
Who owns white horn? What do you own?
Oh shit, that was excellent. What do you own?
In dress like judgment day
Talking smoke like it's holy flame
Name drop fear then hide your hand
Throw a stone then blame the glass
You build a myth out of whispers fit
Paint me black with the words you spread
Call the truth when it's staged and lit
Whole performance built on counterfeit
You play games with the frame, try to rhyme it
You call it one and I call it theater
A costume of virtue at ground to feed
There you move like a queen on a crooked board
Stack the deck then preach reward
Fake moral panic, selective grace
Point one finger with three at your face
Like glow in a dead-eyed room
Trying to sell me my own doom
But I know the trick, I know the trade
Fear gets loud when the lies afraid
You can dress it up in righteous light
You can flood the stage and pick a fight
But truth, don't break
Truth cuts through the projection screen
Okay, so I guess like it's continue
Yeah
Okay, I'll just read a little bit more
Just to just like an address and stuff we're back and see
There's no one's really
Then I'll then I'll be
Done with it. I will. I mean, I'm not gonna be going to
Samans anymore not going to beat us anymore. I
Have no reason to talk about Christine. I'm not gonna go. I'm not gonna go talk to any of these people
So I guess they they want to respond to this video
I'll give them that and I won't respond to them, but unless it's like
something that I have to respond to like legally but
I don't know if you're hearing that there's threats of violence being made, there's anti-Semitism,
there is...
I mean, I'm the only white person that has been not only called the N-word, but I experienced
not only homophobia, I experienced anti-Semitism, and racism, I'm not even Jewish or black,
I loved, I loved those people, but I'm just me, okay?
So, I don't know.
Experience more racism than some black people probably.
Called the N word more than, okay, anyway.
Okay, so let's see, what else do we have?
We just have a couple, a little bit more.
Okay.
Huh, okay, let's see the entertainment but then there's like something else that masquerades is entertainment
But it actuality is pure evil or very evil. I don't play with evil, you know I
Come from what I think could be possibly viewed as one of the most controversial arms the entertainment industry the adult entertainment industry
But even in the adult entertainment industry, there are certain energies that are not messed with
People got together and they agreed. Okay. We'll take it this far. We won't take it, you know this far, you know
This doesn't seem to be the same level of restraint within these communities of yet
One day there will be one or not right now, and I'm not willing to put my life my being at risk
When it comes to people like the fraudulent psychic who they not only have nothing left to lose
But they're like this close to no longer even being you know
So there is no whatever her name is cycle. I'll just call her Monica, right?
There's no Monica cycle anyone that I don't want to talk to anymore
You're never gonna hear from me again. You don't even exist to me
I don't I'm not receptive to people who trying to force me to interact with them
I'm too much of a big girl for that
Anyone that needs to be forgiven has already been forgiven. I've already apologized whoever I need to apologize. That's it
So you're some faceless loser who's never met me. Don't speak on me like you know me, okay?
Don't say she has no real emotions when you don't know me. Don't say I'm an alcoholic when you don't know me
Don't say shit about me. You don't know me unless you really want to get to know me because there's some of you
To where I don't think
I know who you are, and I have completely clean criminal history.
It would be nothing for me to punch some of you in your fucking face, at all.
And I'll take the charge. I don't care. Not at this point. Not at this point.
But the fraudulent psychic I was only around him a total of maybe four hours. He smells full of cat hair
Doesn't brush his teeth doesn't take care of himself mentally ill has taken money for more people than he should have
And he's made more promises to people than he should have and they're about to come after him
Okay, I've pityed him. I felt like let me
Nice because I had some people be kind and nice to me throughout my life
I'm very fortunate very grateful very appreciative, but I'm not a taker
Don't make threats to get my way. I don't cry. I don't do any of that crap. Thank you
You know, there's somebody in these communities known as what's his name big Vegas? He's right when he says keep your distance
Yeah, I'm naturally a very social person. I'd like to be social I've
Been a little bit of an introvert over the past few years those of you who know me, okay more private information
But I'm going to be I'm back to being me again. I'm back to being social. I'm back to having fun
I'm back to being productive. I'm back to being a real person and real people like me. Don't um put up
Weirdos can't show their face. I don't know. I know I don't look my best right now
But I purposely came on here on video because I want y'all to know I mean what I say. That's why I use my government name
And then she says her entire name, okay.
I'm not always right, but I mean what I say.
And I'm not looking to exploit people.
I'm not looking to use or abuse people
because that's what's going on in these communities right now.
A lot of very abusive, nasty, gross, disgusting people.
I kind of think part of the reason
that a lot of people do keep their cameras off
is because they're dirty, you know?
You got a lot to give to the good times of her life.
He's messy.
I don't think he's dirty.
I think he's messy, but he always has a camera on.
You see?
Who is he?
Don't you?
You see who he is, don't you?
He may speaks a lot just like me, but you see him.
And he doesn't beg.
There have been times when he's been bratty, but he doesn't beg.
In that fraudulent psychic, I feel like has stolen a lot of his personality.
It's weird when I really think about it, from the screen on the wall, to his outfit.
And I would like to know exactly why Good Times is not on YouTube anymore.
It's because someone did shut down his channel, and if so, who did?
You know?
I know it's that someone you don't like him.
I don't like him, but it's almost like he was pushed aside to make way for others.
And that's not quite right, not at all.
Yeah.
Yeah, blackout, Andy.
You and I are similar.
We don't always agree, but I see why you get upset.
I do see why.
And you are just being upset about certain things, without a doubt.
But that's all I have to say.
I don't want to take up too much of y'all's time.
I feel like whoever needed to hear me has heard me,
but if I don't talk to you anymore,
it's because you're not compatible or worth my time.
My time is valuable.
I have really started to realize
how short life actually is.
And to me, at this point,
just considering what's going on in these communities,
it's a waste of my time.
I've said more than I think I should have said,
and I'm happy.
Said a lot of what was on my mind and I'm happy I was able to essentially be a translator for some of you out there
Who aren't exactly able to put into words how you're feeling. Bye
It's just the energy of some of these people who are dominating the equation.
I don't like them.
And I don't want to have any association with me.
I don't want to have any association with me.
I don't want people to think that they know me when they don't.
I don't want them to name-drop me when they have bad intentions, because even if people
come to me later and they're like, does so-and-so know you?
They're talking about you.
And I'm like, nope.
And they're like, oh, I didn't think so.
Still, I just don't like that.
Maybe I'm a little bit of a snob, but so what?
That's me.
so let me look at the chat real quick before I get going um no I'm not going to post the link um
I'll tell you I'm going to make you some highlights I need to cover you to black out you know when I
have some time I'm bored I'm going to do some streams that are positive about you that are
educational when it comes to ip2 grams because grams because you know whether I agree with
certain things y'all say or not you two are og's you are just og's when it comes to these
I revisited some things when it came to Schemask Andy.
There's a few.
But what I want to do, caution some of you about,
don't let others who don't know you, who you are,
tell your story, because that's what people
are attempting to do right now.
Aren't they really, right?
Don't let people who have walked alongside you, who have not
walked alongside you ever.
And no matter what industry you're in,
no matter what you're doing,
don't ever let anyone else who's not a real witness
to who you are tell your freaking story.
Don't.
That's good advice.
Maybe I'll take that advice.
Maybe I won't let her tell my story, right?
Okay, name your own storyteller if it's not yourself.
I think you should always be yourself personally, but.
You see what I'm saying because you got people right now trying to basically steal your soul. Don't let them do it
You know don't let yourself be an imitated or duplicated make it known that you're an original that's very important because
If you don't make it known that you do not fight for yourself,
if you do not retain your individuality, then you've lost.
People will notice and they'll try to take it from you.
Don't let them. You're too valuable for that.
And for God's sake, do not put any stalker credibility into someone who hides.
If someone cannot show his face, they cannot tell you their name.
That is linked to personal accountability and they know damn well something is fucking wrong.
So have a good night. Blackout.
Thanks for coming in here.
Whoever else is watching,
you're probably watching Good Times.
You're probably watching Good Times.
Have a good night.
The only, oh, the letter Q.
You have so much growing up to do.
It's funny to me.
I'm glad to know you,
but use a little filter a bit more.
In this case, I'm glad you didn't.
Think before you spoke tonight.
Be careful what you say,
especially when you're talking about someone
who does authentically like you.
Have a good night.
Bye-bye.
Authentically like you.
Oh, if you like some authentically,
I guess you didn't like authentically like me, right?
Feels so dumb. Why am I so dumb? I actually I don't feel dumb because
Think what happened was exactly what was supposed to happen
Let me see the chat
Okay
And this is also really handy tonight because I can see
Just who's the bullshitter. Let me see like I'm in good times are horrible. Oh my god. She's hiding in the past. Oh
Hold on.
Did I transcribe that?
I transcribe that.
No, yeah, I sent there with like a feather quill
and I wrote it down.
Okay.
Selfie.
I can't even transcribe.
Of course I use AI to transcribe it.
Okay, we're talking, okay.
I mean, it's like, selfie.
Are you trolling me, selfie?
Come on.
Yeah.
Shan?
Hey.
With the flip is going on here. I just reading a transcript. Okay, you might want to rewind the beginning and find out
You're late. Okay, I
Like both people and you're staying you're not finding anyone's battles. Okay
You stop going on panels when they had a large small volume of stalkers and we were saying random outrageous things. Yeah
That I should too. Yeah, I'm going to too only as of late though the Jew talk gets people going really
I would never like that. I wasn't reading a script. I was reading the transcript from her show Amanda
Okay
Okay, so this is the point
I mean, I don't think people are, like, really listening to me.
Like, I don't think people will get it.
I'm trying to explain to you.
Okay.
I know.
I'm not at all upset with what you said because it's just bullshit, right?
I mean, if I smell and I don't brush my teeth and I...
I'm just like so ugly and
I'm a fraudulent psychic. Why did she purchase so many psychic readings from me? Why did she have so many?
Where were we planning to get it together for our birthday after we had that dinner?
Why we're supposed to smile and we had the best time like like really so this is where I'm gonna be sorting out with the trolls
And it's like, you know get if you get like really kicked out today. Don't come back
Okay
Okay, and so this person, Janny, you are banned forever.
If anyone sees Janny in the chat,
is my, any mods here, any mods that I can take seriously?
Or is this like troll mods and troll people in the chat?
Christine said my mother's name?
Are you serious?
Let's see.
Be in a sausage with okay, so let's see some people talking about their drink. Don't tell me what to do
Okay
Um
It's like it's it's getting there's so many trolls to deal with I do need like mods to like kind of watch out
Like if it's someone's obviously just being in a fucking troll and it's like right can you just like we help me out a little bit?
But I can take care of it
Looks like there's some
Interesting
Okay
Yes, I know Jesus's friends Jesus's family and friends were Jewish. I mean
Thank you, Abed. Thank you so much. I think I'm
Norman I cannot I know we can't rationalize insanity, but I'm trying to like
First of all, I'm not the first person, but I think I'm like I don't know why I'm so singled out as you know
Everyone else is like they could have their name
They still still mention their name even though she said you're saying horrible thing, but she asked it's had my new name
Is a slanderous thing? I
Didn't do anything to this woman really I
Mean it's like I just don't I just don't know sometimes
Go ahead
I know you can't be a 24-7 man. I'm just like saying you you can
Okay, I don't know. Oh
Thank you. You like the space. Oh, oh, yeah, you like this. This is um, yeah
Thank you so much. Thank you for the backdrop. It's actually but it's I guess I just copied you know it from good times
I guess he's he would he's the adventure of the green screen, you know, because that's what you know
She said actually I was able to like talk on on on a good time show and I had a good time
I had a good I had a good time with good times, right?
I know man, that's what I think if you look,
I think I did a buddy troll presentation
where it's all about how they're like,
they get your trust and then they get you to like,
you know, reveal a lot of stuff
and then they will use that as leverage
and all this kind of stuff.
So it's, yeah, it's kind of like,
that's my lesson for the day to everybody is like,
there's obvious trolls
and the obvious trolls will be easy enough to kick out.
I mean, I keep being so RG around
and Arthur and stuff, cause I like them,
You know
Yeah, okay, the mask does slip off yes, Mina and like but that this thing and it's like yeah, did I have the whether like
She's really she's I'll say she's a she's pretty good at it. She's really good at what she does like really really good
Really good
But so my I'm not like
I'm not in some like, some chooch off the turnip truck, okay?
I just fall off the tune of truck.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you so much, Joey.
Did I see all the inscribbles go out at last night?
Oh, I didn't see that.
No, I'm kind of like,
Not really on too many shows
You were enjoying the good times show this morning and then the drama came in see
I know see some people like just like talking about interesting things like I love I love talking about the Charles Manson
Like I was talking with them good times this morning
We're talking about Charles Manson and the Beatles and fun stuff and then all of a sudden
Ding dong
The witches here it was Christine at the door
And I was trying to apologize to her and stuff and I was trying to I was I was actually like oh Christine come on
I was like get her a look. I want to talk to her and stuff and then she just starts attacking me
And I was like Christine. I know that I saw the comment on that video
There was just basically there was a trip kick video was just basically me
retelling the stories and everything all that they added in with some witch graphics and stuff like that so and she laughed in the comments
So I was like, oh, she might have a sense of humor. No, she doesn't she just came in to say that
She can say to me in all honesty to jump off a bridge, but when I say
In response to clumsy saying you think Christina Beter are doing a ritual on you
And I was like, yes, I cried in the ether.
I saw them dancing around a tree, you know,
sacrificing baby goats.
Or maybe a euphemism for baby goats.
Okay.
And then that's considered,
she takes that seriously.
She also said, stop talking about Bita and Emma
and me and Sam-Man.
Oh my God, talk about.
There's all of you are just saying all the worst shit about me
And I think you're having your own three-hour lives and stuff like that all talking about me, and I'm not allowed to talk about you
Okay
I'm not allowed actually this is a talk show in the community
Like you know what send a cease and assist and leave me alone and stop talking about me too. How about that when you do that?
Maybe I'll do that
But until you do I don't want you out there just fucking slandering my name anymore. It's like
because really
It's getting like ridiculous, it's getting fucking ridiculous, right? I don't know
So I'm not gonna lose my cool. I'm just like gonna calm down. Okay
You know, I know I get I get hyped up. I'm just my I'm just like
Being myself, you know, this is like raw. This is real
This is not like fake, you know.
Community is toxic, it is toxic, but you know what?
I can start to drain the swamp.
If I get down to zero people and stuff,
and actually it won't be zero people,
it'll be at least a few people.
I'll have at least three people
that will come in once in a while still.
Yeah, I guess they will, I mean, if I stop talking about the drama, I guess, like, you know, nobody's going to come here anymore, but maybe I'll talk about what I want to talk about, you know, I don't, I don't constantly need to be told that I'm wrong by people.
I'm not saying you did. I'm saying, like, you know, constantly told, oh, this and this and this, run your show like this.
You should have known that you I mean it's like I told you so this I'm right now just presenting this to you
You can make your own shit. I didn't slander her at all. All I did was read all I did was read her own words, okay?
Are you talking to Amber do you what person what person's first amendment right like you're talking about chat or mine?
Because on YouTube
You love Bita and Samman and well, I love Bita and Samman too until Bita struck my channel and Samman porn ball me
Okay
Now I have a different opinion thank you selty appreciate that
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't see the first part of the message.
Let me see.
Go, go, go.
Difficult take away, okay, hold on.
Oh, hold on, I missed it, I'm sorry.
Everyone talks about everyone,
and just like I say,
everyone is sending a cease and desist
and not legally actionable
unless they actually follow through with a lawyer
and even that kid's extreme.
Yeah, I know.
I'm saying like, but you can send,
like you can like draft one of them
and they send it at least,
and it's like, then the person will probably not like stop.
Like, you know, it's like, you can say,
you can make a request,
please stop talking about me to somebody.
And then,
I know you don't necessarily need a lawyer. I mean for it, but you know, it's like usually people will, you know
Yeah, I got you. I got you
Yeah, I do remember you saying long ago that you could follow other on other streams that people follow me
I don't believe you until you saw it for yourself. Maybe this morning. You couldn't go another shoes up people following
Oh, so who is that? Yeah
Sometimes it gets confused when the check is really confusing because there's a lot of people talking into different
We're talking to each other sometimes
I think they're talking to me and it's like where I missed messages and so I do apologize if I get it wrong sometimes
I try my best
You're about time eating nothing but Tina's burritos. I hope they're good
Basically, she said, I will be hurt, and I don't know, it just felt threatening, not
like with that, it's on the web, I read the transcript, but as for that, otherwise, hey,
I used to be calling me ugly and stupid and dirty and smelly and animal abuser and all
this kind of stuff.
Maybe
Maybe like, you know, I could get a manicure once in a while more, right? I don't know. But you know what I
Don't think you know, they're usually cleanliness sometimes
It's a cleanliness equals God. Yeah, Sam and Sam and a horn bomb me
You can't you know why because he was mad that I had some people in my chat
I even have more people in my chat because he's playing Street Fighter
Even he had then had like a few more people but he got really I heard him
I went over to his chat and I heard him like complaining about it
And then he came over here and he formed on me to try to like give me a stop
So people would go and watch him play fucking Street Fighter. I mean, it's like
Lame
So lame
And Bita struck my channel and it's like so but what did I really say about Bita?
They named a spider after me and then like flushed it down the toilet and said it was a secret spider ritual that I should
And I should watch out and so maybe maybe I could take that as a joke whatever, but you know
It's this other woman's like what if what if a man what if a man what if I made an AI where I put a woman in
burning dumpster like I was put in a burning dumpster like did you like you
guys have seen like some of this some of this art she made of me right like I'm
not like because some people haven't seen it like I try to show Christine she
would she wouldn't she refused to look at it yeah like did you see this and she
also told him good times good time said that she told good times that she would
throw me and him in an oven because we're Jews okay
Oh, I got I got rid of the strikes. I got the rid of the strikes. Yeah
So I
Think that's supposed to be bet middler from what's that movie like focus focus with the Sanderson's and I think that is like
Who's that fat guy and then in the Yankees hat? I don't know who that is and I think that's Jesus in the dumpster
Yeah
So what if what if a man made that with a woman in the dumpster? What did that be considered like?
Really
Like I mean, I think probably like, you know, he would go to prison or something like that
I mean or at least you'd be like, oh my god. It's just like when I played this like this funniest clip
There's a funny clip where this dolphin I
Know yeah, oh, that's beta. I thought it was a bed middler from a hocus pocus
My gosh, you guys gray hair like that. Wow, it's quite a look
Okay, oh, yeah, and then there's this one too
I mean, it's not like it's not like she's saying I should be crucified on a cross or anything, right?
Of course, it's not gonna go that far where she would actually like, you know, think I should be on a cross, right?
You know, she would never go that far, right?
Where I'd actually be like hanging off of a cross. Oh, wait
Oops
Yeah, but look at mine and then look at bakelifts and then look at the one I did of her
I mean I won't show the one I did of her you can look at my community wall if you want to it's very it's actually very very mild
Okay
Um, I know it's the AI, but did you hear about being threatened to beat me up?
I should be on a, I shouldn't have never been born.
I'm just like, I'm, I'm fraudulent.
That's what she called me as, as like a name fraudulent.
Um, you know.
Oh, and then, oh, and, oh, and what about like, yeah, you really should guys,
you need to catch up if you don't, if you just say you're coming in and you're seeing like,
how about the start of the beginning of the show?
I can only explain it so many times without saying,
oh, why are you so I'm talking about?
Well, because people keep asking me to explain it again.
I mean, geez.
But not like I'm making out with her ex-boyfriend, right?
That would just be too, oh my God.
Okay, well would anybody like to
Come up what it does anybody have anything to say does anybody?
Hi, I'm Marty yo you
Monkey ears over ears me. What does that mean?
The purge begins July 2nd
What is there's a purge house Marty the NBA shut down and went to announce
Magic announced he had a disease. Do you believe in magic? Oh, he doesn't have that anymore
All right, what you're just sending a lot of weird stuff, okay
Anybody have any any questions any any comments any
Anything they want to say
Are my feelings hurt? No. Because I'm a strong person and it's like I love myself and I know the truth.
It hurts is like that you know there's a lot of people that just don't even care but you know what
I think I did a pretty good uh pretty good pretty good uh presentation you might want to like go back
Kind of will explain a lot. I hope maybe if you ever have a problem, maybe it will help you
Can we do a carpool to see what you found out today? It's true about you being uh-oh
Is that true because once I had actually I had like I had a vision of
The thing called the honey ritual or my I saw someone in the cemetery
They go hole and take my picture and cover it with honey and then bury it
Tell the honey Michelle
Big time no, but I mean I did I did mean
You saw you can you saw those you saw her you saw those aides and she also did a thumbnail of it
Okay, so I will just momentarily I
Did a nice AI of her okay, and just as imagine and you just ask yourself the question. It's not being positive or negative, okay?
Just imagine and just ask yourself this question. Okay, and then that I'll just end the show with this. Okay
Okay, I
Don't but that it was just it was just phrasing it in an unusual way which I don't think
I mean, if you even if it's true or not, you know, it's just like don't just they say it's not true. Okay
That's all that that's the only one I'm gonna do. Okay. Is anybody gonna laugh? No, okay. Well, that was it so
See no one even laughed at it so
That was too nice, right
But I'm not I'm not here to hurt people, you know, and I do care about her and I was a real friend
I didn't do anything to her. I didn't do anything to Christine. These are all words, right?
It's like at the end of the day, I can stand up for myself. I understand that was standing
up for myself because I'm trying to help people and stuff.
It's like Arthur. It's like I just feel like I
Already kicked you out once and then I like let you back in and then you said something stupid again
So I even take try one more time
You can bother
Thank you, thank you as Jx Rose
I'm not trying to be vengeful
I am I think this is that a big time if you watch the whole show
I did a whole presentation about buddy trolling and like the whole I
Exposed the whole blueprint of it. And so that's my revenge
and
Hopefully it will help people you can go and rewind the episode and watch that and maybe I'll clip clip that part out and
Put it in the
Get on its own. Yeah, go back and check it out because it's a really good presentation stuff. Thank you and
So and I didn't I did make it like a you know, more a more formal statement. I don't want I don't want this to keep going on forever
I don't want to like it to escalate and stuff. I'm not trying to get it to escalate, but I'm not gonna be
bullied into silence, okay
Arthur I will give you one more chance
If you say something stupid to me, I will never talk to you again. Okay?
Hey, Psych, I appreciate you allowing me beyond on the platform.
I do want to apologize to Christine.
Yesterday, I did say something offensive to her.
And like you said, you've done nothing or said anything to her.
Well, I didn't say I didn't say something but it was a joke. I mean I said something right
I didn't like I mean and she would talks about me too
I mean it's like she said I should jump off a bridge right and so and she said she meant it I said I
Saw in my vision
Dancing around a tree, you know
sacrificing baby goats and it was a joke and
somehow
I'm wrong and bad and she's writing good, right?
It was clearly a joke because you are being so outlandish with it.
It's just obviously a joke.
Now, have you said something about her, you know, about where she used to work, about nursing?
Nothing. Nothing. Nothing personal. I didn't talk to anything.
But it was so outlandish. It was like me saying, oh, Sandman, at the swamp that you live in, you know,
I hope Fiona and you, you know, go away. You know, it's like, it's just a joke.
My I'm a Capricorn so I am I'm a goat and it's like so I'm very against the sacrifice of goats or anything
So I I do feel like I don't know about you
I do feel like and this community could probably be an example of it how
Everyone has become so soft to
Comments to jokes
everything is just no no why would you say that that's offensive I try to be
joke I try to joke around and then it's like then I get like serious threats and
I get serious like hate and serious defaming and serious like I get I get
the serious and this stuff and I get that people get mad at me I've never
seen I get projected on you know oh yeah and
I'm not gonna forget like the other day. Oh, I love Christine. I don't know who the women all the women she's talking about
By the way, she didn't mention. She's like Alisa told you to leave her the fuck alone. I
Never had a conflict with Alisa
Like and so I don't understand what she's talking about. I mean Alisa's discord Alisa probably would have kicked me out of her discord
Which is yeah, I don't know why she's like I'm maybe like white knighting or gatekeeping you from other
Content creators
She wants to control the narrative. Okay. She wants to be the one to control the narrative for everyone. Okay
Well, I'll let you be that because I have my own cult codex and she thinks I stole the idea from her
Wait, it was a wiki. So are you?
Whatever is whatever your name is last name wiki. No, so it's it's like something that
A lot of people have done, right?
It's like, I can have a show
and compile information about it.
I'm allowed to.
I'm not gonna blackmail anybody.
It's not controlled by Bita or Sandman.
I'm not, but I wanna say, I was not approached.
I was not paid a large sum of money by anybody
to create a cast, okay?
A cast of people.
And I'm not involved in organized crime.
I mean, there's just like so many outlets
and I don't condone the murdering of...
you know, she's like burying her babies and stuff. I mean, it's just like crazy.
The things I mean, it's huge. Yes, like, thank you. Thank you. You're welcome. Have a nice day.
Yeah, your buddy has locked horns in the past. Yeah. But at the end of the day, you know,
that person I'm talking about, like, like that I read, we have the same birthday. Okay.
And I believe in very heavily in astrology, right?
Right and that what they're like, um, see I would and I would never tell somebody dude
Don't do this on your show. Don't do this on your show. Don't talk about this person. Don't talk about this person
I mean, it's like at the end of the day
I'm allowed to talk about whoever I want and
Especially I'm allowed to
Respond if people are talking about me and doing three-hour lives where they're like standing around a toilet saying they're doing a secret spider ritual
And they named the spider after me and drowned a spider
And then they're like, well, what is he so weird?
It's just weird.
And you're saying I'm weird for doing carol cards and stuff,
but I'm fake second anyway, so right?
By the way, my readings are for entertainment purposes only.
I'm not claiming to have any powers
that somebody else doesn't have.
Like people all have the power of intuition and empathy
or most people do, right?
It seems like maybe some people
are a little bit lacking in it around here,
One thing about me is I do have empathy. I am forgiving if someone was to get even after all this any of these people
genuinely came to me and we're like
hey
You know, I was mad at you because you did this but maybe I maybe I
Did something to and maybe we're all just human and we have bad days
But no, I'm the monster. I'm gonna be told whatever like I'm just just a monster, right? So
because there's this narrative being pushed.
I'm not trying to control the narrative.
I'm just trying, I actually showed her an error.
I just used her words.
I didn't write in makeup that she said dirty Jews
and stuff like that.
That was what she decided to say at her mouth.
I didn't make her say good times
and I should be pushed in an oven.
That was her that said that, okay?
I think that she might, should be reminded that Jesus,
like I said, Jesus would be, you know,
Jesus would be turning over on his cross right now
if he heard what she was saying, okay?
If she walked hand in hand with Jesus,
they must be handcuffed together or something.
You don't choose a side, well.
What if one side is like obviously going too far I
Didn't make any threats of violence towards anybody. I didn't insult anybody's hygiene. I never said anything about her
her her her
The smell of any parts of her body because she said I she said I smell and she said I'm disgusting
But yet, the next day, she said, let's go to Hollywood,
or I had to sit in the car, or I got to sit in the car,
or I sat in the car for like an hour next to her.
You'd think if I was just like so disgusting,
she would have like said, oh, and so just vile.
She would have said, okay, well, the dinner was nice.
Bye, and that would have been it.
But she decided.
And then she has a special saying I didn't smell after that and she because people asked. Oh, how was psyche?
She said he's just as great as he is on a show on and in that you guys remember when she liked me
You could you really hate everyone. Okay. Well, at least that's honest
I would say
Yeah, like completely made up and the other is highly exaggerated. Okay, but okay, but I guess I got my point out
and I don't know when I'm gonna see you guys again because
Maybe it's just time for me to like take a step back a little bit like you know
Yeah, I remember that but also
It's called it's called like, you know, she she she she did like kind of
Pull a fast one on me. So actually, but I'm maybe I knew but maybe I need to experience things for myself
Maybe that's the only way some people learn. So thank you guys. Love you. You have a great day. Okay, and guys
love yourselves and love each other and
Be kind to each other even
Maybe to the the guy who kind of gets you know, maybe like he has a dirty fingernails or something
So, love you, thank you so much.